(Susan:)Very nice, Wyatt.
(Susan:)And you wonder why this one
turned out the way he did.
(Randall:)You see what I've gotta
put up with!
(Susan:)What you've gotta put up with?
(Susan:)Why did you have
to go to jail?
(Randall:)It's called getting
caught, Mother!
Hello!
Hey, there he is!
Hey!
Oh, Leonard! It's so
nice to see you again!
Oh, you, too!
(Leonard:)Hey, everyone, this is
my mother, Beverly.
(Howard:)- Hello.
- Hi.
We are not white trash!
(Amy:)Are you excited to see your son
walk down the aisle?
(Alfred:)Yes, I am.
(Alfred:)I'm just feeling
a little guilty
(Alfred:)about all the trouble
I've caused.
(Mary:)Oh, so am I.
(Sheldon:)You made God sad today, Mom.
(Amy:)Sheldon, they haven't done
anything wrong.
(Amy:)I think it's nice
they're hitting it off.
(Sheldon:)Well, that's still no reason
to rush into anything.
(Sheldon:)Look at us.
(Sheldon:)We took things
remarkably slow.
(Sheldon:)You and I, we didn't even
hold hands for two years.